{
    "subject": "resource/Jesus_of_Montreal",
    "predicate": "ontology/editing",
    "object": "resource/Isabelle_Dedieu",
    "human_readable": "Jesus of Montreal was edited by Isabelle Dedieu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9067243337631226,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Isabelle Dedieu and the film 'Jesus of Montreal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637278079986572,
            "question": "Who edited the film 'Jesus of Montreal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8582789897918701,
            "question": "Which film did Isabelle Dedieu edit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8521463871002197,
            "question": "Who was responsible for editing 'Jesus of Montreal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8394867181777954,
            "question": "Name a film edited by Isabelle Dedieu."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7872806787490845,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of the editor for 'Jesus of Montreal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021145820617676,
            "question": "What is the name of the film editor who worked on 'Jesus of Montreal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379699110984802,
            "question": "What film is associated with Isabelle Dedieu's work as an editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6265707612037659,
            "question": "If you were to watch 'Jesus of Montreal,' who would you credit for its editing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5595960021018982,
            "question": "What is the title of the film that Isabelle Dedieu worked on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jesus of Montreal was edited by Isabelle Dedieu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1028_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to watch 'Jesus of Montreal,' who would you credit for its editing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1028_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is associated with Isabelle Dedieu's work as an editor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1028_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film editor who worked on 'Jesus of Montreal'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1028_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1028_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information does not mention Isabelle Dedieu as the editor of Jesus of Montreal. In fact, it mentions Denys Arcand et al. as the authors and creators of the film, but there is no mention of an editor named Isabelle Dedieu."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the editing credits for \"Jesus of Montreal,\" so there is no support in the given context to confirm or deny that Isabelle Dedieu was the editor. Therefore, based on the available information, it cannot be concluded whether the statement is true or false."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context to suggest that Jesus of Montreal was edited by Isabelle Dedieu.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Isabelle Dedieu as an editor in any of the provided text information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Isabelle Dedieu as the editor of Jesus of Montreal in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Isabelle Dedieu as an editor of the film. There is no provided information supporting her role in the editing process.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}